no this
she
[Music]
hey my C in my paper
excuse me sir can you remove
I what have you
spoke can't you all
con get short if you don't stop now I'll
be walking out of your
classes Jesus
[Music]
M
JY this
[Music]
man what Master they
you you Beed
me I be she taking my pen
yes you a p
Jesus give me my P I
want of you run stood up and left my
class before I chained
you deserve
why English she my own Jesus no it is
me don't mind she and her
areed What's happen no you should talk
to me what happen
here are you playing what Tye of is both
of the pass upon
me deser
St they are starting to
4:30
of
corrector you will say Happy New Years
I you you
there no she's not me with
you okay if he did it that did he didn't
did it if he didn't did it that didn't
he he didn't did it
give me that give me that give me that
now take your Foodies and your water
okay
okay I
forgot I to give you this your are you
playing what type of play is this who's
that that's my
mommies come and beat me you no don't
worry Master if you would
that did you dided inequality of the
balanced equation because of your
Fe you right give me your hand me
[Music]
me oh not
good you see yesterday he killed many
people but today be very careful don't
kill much people
Jesus who that my daddy it's an assassin
hey I'm not beating you again
Master assignment no assignment who's
that
that all right no
assignments enough is enough sir I toed
them will but the
brilliant theyed us
well are you the new English teacher yes
I
have you have yes I was push in here
what my to do what to be a thought of
your
student are you understood
yes you your time is finished how no I
haven't time one
minute
imagination spoken corrected Jesus we
conc you
some justification with Mery shut your
mouth if you V Contin fighting you may
end up hting who didn't fored you why
fighted soting
off no it is she sir ma is she spelling
as she or she no it is she
hey no dness it's in she see you what
did he
n five times how many books do you count
I WR J 15
times who my da bad
English is me is
she oh now why want to
tell you a not me who learned how bad
English
[Music]
is this your laugh is making my laugh to
laugh keeper I the
B don't mind that that's how she
beh no it's no yet times
[Applause]
you're not afraid of me at
all sir can I the rooms why want to
visit
me what I got some my eyes he F
away I saw him eting the food
you master our food is not
suited delicious
not are you playing what type of playe
is it uh how dare you watching football
in the classes are a
stadium no I'm not a stadium I watch it
online can I watch yes all
[Music]
what master I knew it
Miss ARA chemistry of Oran
Nebuchadnezzar Valen compliment of the
Valentine
SE are you
playing corrector you will sa Happ
Valentine's
Day my
Valen this copy
me you
are why me master let me explain that
hey explained or explanate I'm
discouragement in your
English if I never copied you I should
pass out my
examination God have Mery upon usop me
because you didn't understood what
Master
yesterday uhoh
you think want Ming
me bu not good
[Music]
are you a bday of today of cousin how
many years are
she I'm
[Music]
13 me
now you will say I cling years old
[Music]
Jesus you kicking the
ball and what F
now I didn't get it
internationally
what instead of you to be readed your
book you're busy playing football as oh
not
good okay I forgive you now let's say
[Laughter]
[Music]
now please please please please okay
please please
okay what I want you
to D I said don't talk this is coming
don't greet
him H good
oh not
good mon May went out the M of me was by
my
nose PR have you balanced de
how much is your school for a new
student for a new student okay excussion
and lesson fee everything is
2,500 Jesus how are you so as I
say master she's speaking the LI I
didn't Dr it
internationally wait wa let me explanate
you she and he shut
up let's continue
sir let me
explain you
know and the leg is from the
blood Master
him come down sir look I'm not
coming we are breaking
PRC
[Music]
hey h what she tooking I my Gala is the
G yours yes it is my
yours can't to let English see
you who do you be who do
you you know how how many years you
objected my master I see everything that
happen okay it's all catastrophe of un
intention internationality of the
incorporative that happen between
the my here can't beiz due to the idce
of EXP
[Music]
concerning
students welcome to the
excussion jesuses I want to show you
some beautiful
animales so now can somebody tell me the
name of this animac master it is
oxygen
no awes
so you don't know this animal okay it is
ois you are saying blood this is
assassination where's your
master master
you you cannot answer me
[Music]
H come
here are you your master I'm not your
master it's a lie I knew the
master okay Master
[Music]
is master
are you the master me I'm not the master
oh student am I your
master
master what is master I told you not to
call me master again I'm your master not
master simple English
master oh not good Master can you
your lik you are finally implicate
yourself all because of denomination
J who that Master make a and
interrogate master I'm not the offenses
of you are
not oh this is coming not good
silence
H com in are
you com
in man of God please let me to cast out
bad English away from the students
especially
I in the real of the spirit main looking
see the
ground to the of this R princi are you
sure this man power I have SE I have S
sanor I have I
have I'm a churches of your members Jes
I told you this woman don't have power
my
[Music]
pastor my pastor of miss
disapp this
man why do you reap me my master can
never delay of repentance someone of
reing
youness orness
y okay is the master that
mey
again but Master what have you did your
master liap me on my gift
card my Bitcoin
to clap
clap not good who the master that my my
gift hey ah run master all because you
do don't want to trade with tress score
you have finally put your likess in Pro
mation you know me master back welcome
to school
and if you know you can't Sparkle a
readily made English please keep this
be every time you be spoking big English
don't you know it breaking
our Master my NSE is De I have
catastrophy are
you it is catastrophy
catastrophy what's wrong with you is
your
blind yeah
H you you dis wrong English run I will
show you
today you I am going to kill you
[Music]
round two
fight do you want to
me spoke your English tiny
you mon huh what I'm water and she on my
face my interally did not accept
my master okay we mentally need to make
few banishment of ab away from the
interior of the exterior of this
classroom
concern what's wrong with you I love the
Artic of your English man if it is a
English man nobody can be a competition
of of BL if I'm spoking my dictionary
English detection because I'm the over
best this man yes or No Yes master no
ask them a
question so answer the question yes or
No Yes
master read out the question from the
passage okay
the
attack was cost
by spell it out and pronounce it s e n o
p h o b i
c you couldn't pronunciation s e n o b h
o b i c
bonification
mango
[Music]
next
flash next okay
R
[Music]
chiny popcorn
okay okay
Jesus
teacher
you master you are afraid
Sky SC
isue you where are you coming from no I
for the pollution of dedication in the
forest uhuh you didn't know how to pron
the diation h i I said it is
determination shutting up your mouth
instead of you to calling Master to the
interpretation of difficulties was you
are busy saying
nonsense what's going on here thank God
you are here help us to spell
determination go to your classes no
where there R now SPL this for them sir
SP this for
them QP AF
[Music]
why you like that Master it's because
the boy is square in shape this one
square or
rectangle reang reang now say let me
show you how to play okay you first
check the angle of projection of the B
check the weight of the B weigh 70 km
hour check the angle of distension and
the angle of Ascension then you check
the move back move back check of your
leg make your leg is moving then you
look at the keeper straight forward and
you do want you
fire you are
finally for
[Music]
come back
here the commissioner of
[Music]
Education I be asking a question answer
Meer now answer the
commissioner
okay good now ask them
Divine good come go sit
down Divine da
compications yes brilliant girl answer
the
[Music]
question are you playing what type of
playe is this the communication can be f
as a transer for the In The House of the
in the
commun what is it those tribe or those
tribe is
do now who can sing it for us master I
what is the F tense of get forget forgot
get the
[Music]
answer assignment for me tomorrow
morning
[Music]
are you what
of this
is okay okay okay welcome
sir still laughing teacher why are they
laughing Mr Commissioner of Education
please ignorance the AL together
attitude of their
disrespective it is because all of you
is bicycle are you not
asham we are of your
[Music]
Master you call me again master and she
B my of
M you
of shut
[Applause]
up what language is that somebody
power man of God why are you here I'm
just coming from the mountain I'm fully
prepared I'm prepared
education I can't prepared
physically I all of you one by one
especially
you
hey take you need it what is this shock
absorber call do my everybody say Ste
Jesus everybody say compose your
composition shock you
because of
God of course I'm a proud English
student I love spoken English hey why
are you 14 of course I am the eke keeper
who I want to go the close time of
course I'm the class Captain I love to
correct my classmate wrong English hey
let come come name down of course we are
project English students of course I'm
the English teaching and I Ted them
well masteress